=Reincarnated Love=
=Episode 9=
(Huo Mansion)
Lady Wanyue,
please wait.
I've sent word to Mrs. Huo.
Isn't this Lady Wanyue?
What brings you here?
Indeed.
Ruoli knew I was here,
yet she left me waiting here.
What does she mean?
Mrs. Huo is busy.
Not everyone can meet her.
Lady Wanyue,
you just caused her to lose her child,
and now you've come.
The fact that she's willing to see you
is already generous of her.
Please stay patient
and wait a little longer.
You...
Are you hurt?
It's nothing.
Thank you for your concern.
Sorry, I deserve punishment.
You may leave.
Yes.
May I ask who you are?
My name is Jiang Wanyue.
I'm the second lady of the Jiang family.
I've come to visit Cousin Ruoli.
I am the eldest son of the Huo family,
Lu Huaijin.
You are both graceful and kind.
Your sisterly bond is admirable.
Thank you for your kind words.
You have a noble and composed bearing.
You truly have the bearing of an heir.
Sorry for speaking out of turn.
It's fine.
You indeed
understand me.
Isn't there a man
named Lu Huaijin?
Go and get close to him.
Win his favor.
(I never expected Mr. Lu)
(to be so fond of me.)
Ruoli.
Huaijin, what brings you here?
You've lost your appetite
because of Ruyan.
I had some Jade Shrimp Dumplings made,
but Yanzhi ate
every single one of them.
Thank you, Huaijin.
If you like them, I...
Sorry for the long wait.
I wonder what matters bring you here.
Long time no see.
I came to visit you.
(I'd like to see)
(what tricks you have again.)
Ruoli,
you haven't been resting well lately.
I have a fine blend of calming incense.
I'll have someone deliver it to you,
okay?
Thank you.
(What?)
(Lu Huaijin admires her too?)
Dear.
What is it?
We need to talk.
Yanzhi,
you're hurting her.
Not your business.
(Just as I thought,)
(Lu Huaijin has feelings
for Jiang Ruoli.)
(Jiang Ruoli,)
(you don't deserve this.)
Lady Wanyue,
I must've made a fool of myself.
What a pity.
She doesn't feel the same way.
With your status,
why bring such shame upon yourself?
You're right.
Some things can't be forced.
However,
even if she isn't my wife,
she's still the dearest family member
I'd protect no matter what.
This feeling in my heart
will never change.
Sorry. I can't stay any longer.
Goodbye.
You're hurting me.
Jiang Ruoli,
I know you had a past with him.
But you are my formal wife.
I don't care what you two were before.
Remember who you are.
Stay away from him.
Let me go first.
Huo Linchuan,
he's just a childhood friend.
I...
ظآزWhere shall I seekظآز
ظآزThe traces of your past livesظآز
ظآزI'd spend a lifetime's luck
just for youظآز
ظآزGazing at your figure
for the rest of my lifeظآز
ظآزUntil time grows us oldظآز
ظآزDreams lift the night
where stars grow thinظآز
You belong
only to me.
ظآزThe galaxy stirs;
destiny endlessly returnsظآز
ظآزIf I could, let me guard you this timeظآز
ظآزHow did this feeling beginظآز
ظآزIn each trial, longing deepensظآز
ظآزAcross vast lands, it still shinesظآز
ظآزWhen the night fades,
the moon shines longerظآز
ظآزA fleeting dream
shines through the rainظآز
ظآزThrough three lifetimes,
we never partظآز
ظآزA thousand years of snow
fall into your palmظآز
ظآزHow does love fade awayظآز
ظآزEach thought recalls the pastظآز
ظآزLonging burns into a lasting acheظآز
Huo Linchuan,
I'm tired
of suspicion,
endless schemes,
and the nightmares that never end.
Then,
what are we now,
you and I?
I want you
to marry me.
Alright.
That kiss just now
was not a deal,
nor a momentary arrangement.
Alright.
From this moment on,
whether it's life or death between us,
there shall be no more secrets.
ظآزGazing at your figure
for the rest of my lifeظآز
ظآزUntil time grows us oldظآز
Mr. Huo.
ظآزThe dream shatteredظآز
ظآزLike illusion, yet trueظآز
ظآزLike a restless soulظآز
ظآزHow vagueظآز
ظآزRain and blood, drifting wildظآز
ظآزA blade of frost in dreamsظآز
ظآزLove and hate entwinedظآز
ظآزRise and fall, yet never fadeظآز
ظآزHow can I turn the tides
of this fleeting lifeظآز
ظآزWhen fate falls apartظآز
ظآزMemories return,
carving tears upon my faceظآز
ظآزYet I can't hold onظآز
ظآزOnly warmth remains
where longing once burnedظآز
ظآزLife after lifeظآز
ظآزFated to meet, but never meant to beظآز
ظآزStill, I refuse to bow or yieldظآز
ظآزIn this life, love becomes my bladeظآز
ظآزTo break free from reincarnationظآز
ظآزAll past affairs tangled with regretظآز
ظآزNow shatter apartظآز
ظآزBy fate and karmic ties confinedظآز
ظآزIs this fate or calamityظآز
ظآزIs it life, death, or parting painظآز
ظآزI ask only for a moment of peace,
as devout as my heartظآز
ظآزIn the next life, grant me one kissظآز
ظآزTo kiss the snow upon the brows,
and the depths of your gazeظآز
ظآزFor once we kissed,
destiny bound us to never partظآز
ظآزThis fleeting life feels but a dreamظآز
ظآزSober or indulgeظآز
ظآزI only wish to be with you,
with all my heartظآز